(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T00:25:53.715641",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
“いっせーのー”で鳴り響いたスタートの合図
With a "Ready, set, go!" the start signal rang out,
なぞった線で結んだ世界
Connecting the world with traced lines...
色付けていくここから
...coloring it from here on out.
かくれんぼ
[Title: Hide-and-Seek]
物心がつく頃すでに此処にあった
By the time I was old enough to understand, it was already here.
繋いだ誰かの記憶は 夕日と共に蘇る
The connected memories of someone
revive with the sunset
古ぼけた絵本を飛び出して
Flying out of a worn-out picture book
落書きの中に一つの答えを見つけた
I found a single answer inside the doodles
自分の価値に目を疑って どこまでだって落ちていけるの
Doubting my own worth,
how far down can I fall?
どこか遠くに消えてしまいたい こんな世界じゃ僕は要らない
I want to disappear somewhere far away,
in a world like this I'm not needed
カウントダウンは始まっているよ
The countdown has already begun
いっせーのーで、声を上げて 聞こえてくるんだ
On the count of three, raise your voice,
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気付くもうこんな時間だ
Noticing the length of my own shadow,
it's already this late
一等星が顔を出した 届きそうで手を伸ばした
The brightest star has appeared,
I reached out my hand as if I could touch it
次は僕に付いてきなよ 暗闇でも
Follow me next, even in the darkness
もう一回
One more time!
幕は上がりだした
The curtain has begun to rise
もう一回
One more time!
色付けてく ここから
Adding colors from here on out
10年後の僕らは すれ違いばかりで
Ten years from now,
we only pass each other by
幻想に思いを馳せては 戻れないそう思い込んだ
Lost in fantasies,
I was convinced I could never go back
くたびれた心に追い風を
A tailwind for my exhausted heart
あの頃と変わらない夕日も何とも思わない
I feel nothing even looking at
the same sunset as back then
自分を信じ歩いていければ どこまでだって登れるのにな
If I could just walk believing in myself,
I could climb anywhere
葛藤が繋ぐその空白に 大切なもの見落としている
In the blank space connected by conflict,
I'm overlooking what's important
見つけられないと泣き喚く君へ
To you, crying out that you can't find it
いっせーのーで、声を上げて 聞こえてくるんだ
On the count of three, raise your voice,
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気付くもうこんな時間だ
Noticing the length of my own shadow,
it's already this late
一等賞で駆け抜ける君 くっついてただけの僕でも
Even if I was just clinging to you
as you ran in first place
君の前を歩けるかな こんな頼りない僕でも
I wonder if I can walk ahead of you,
even as unreliable as I am
宝箱はホコリを かぶったまま無くした
The treasure chest was lost, covered in dust
鍵はずっと君の ポケットの中にあった
The key was always inside your pocket
散らばってた全てが 今一つに重なる
Everything that was scattered
is overlapping as one now
手を取り始めよう 僕たちの物語
Let's take each other's hands
and begin our story
もういいかい
Are you ready?
かぶったまま失くした 鍵はずっと
Lost while covered, the key was always...
君のポケットの中にあった
...inside your pocket
散らばってたすべてが
Everything that was scattered...
愛しくて
...is so precious
今一つに重なる
Now overlapping as one
掛け声はいつも
The rallying cry is always...
いっせーのーで、声を上げて
...on the count of three, raise your voice!
いっせーのーで、声を上げて 聞こえてくるんだ
On the count of three, raise your voice,
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気付くもうこんな時間だ
Noticing the length of my own shadow,
it's already this late
一等星が顔を出した 届きそうで手を伸ばした
The brightest star has appeared,
I reached out my hand as if I could touch it
次は僕に付いてきなよ 暗闇でも
Follow me next, even in the darkness
もう一回
One more time!
泣き出した声で
With a tearful voice
もう一回
One more time!
笑う君が見えた
I saw you smiling
もう一回
One more time!
幕は上がりだした
The curtain has begun to rise
もう一回
One more time!
色付けてく ここから
Adding colors from here on out
曇天
作詞・作曲：氏原ワタル
Cloudy Weather
Lyrics & Composition: Wataru Ujihara
鉛の空重く垂れ込み
The leaden sky hangs heavy and low,
真白に澱んだ太陽が砕けて
as the pure white, stagnant sun shatters,
耳鳴りを尖らせる
sharpening the ringing in my ears.
ひゅるりひゅるり低いツバメが
Whirling, whirling, low-flying swallows...
8の字なぞってビルの谷を翔る
...trace figure-eights, soaring through the buildings.
もうじきに夕立が来る
An evening shower will soon be here.
るるる
Ru ru ru...
曇天の道を
Along the cloudy path,
傘を忘れて
having forgotten her umbrella,
歩く彼女は
she walks along,
雨に怯えてる
fearing the rain.
ので僕も
And so, I too,
弱虫ぶら下げて
dragging my cowardice behind me,
空を仰ぐ
look up at the sky.
あちらこちらあんよは上手
Toddling here and there so skillfully,
コーヒー屋に寄って 一休み決めたら
stopping by a coffee shop to take a rest.
帰れない 帰らない
I can't go back, I won't go back.
曇天の道を
Along the cloudy path,
ぶらりぶらぶら
aimlessly wandering,
歩く二人は
the two of us walk along,
足軽の如く
like lowly foot soldiers,
危険好きの誰かのふりをする
pretending to be thrill-seekers.
小心者共
A pair of cowards.
曇天の道を
Along the cloudy path,
傘を忘れて
having forgotten her umbrella,
歩く彼女は
she walks along,
雨に怯えてる
fearing the rain.
ので僕も
And so, I too,
弱虫ぶら下げて
dragging my cowardice behind me,
空を仰ぐ
look up at the sky.
放っといて育つものなんだ なんだろう?
It's something that grows if you leave it alone. What is it?
ももちゃん ももちゃん never never give up!
Momo-chan! Momo-chan! Never never give up!
ももちゃん ももちゃん never give up!
Momo-chan! Momo-chan! Never give up!
Perfect-area complete!
運営さん、なんか放送エコーが切れてるかもしれないとのことで確認お願いします！
Staff, they're saying the broadcast echo might be off, so please check it!
出会いましては簡単すぎるよ
Meeting someone is way too easy.
最初に決めた答えはひとつ
The answer I first decided on is just one.
ときめきまして合格しますか?
My heart throbbed. Do I pass?
恋も勝負もあわてない
No need to rush in love or competition.
コツコツコツと徹夜にため息
Step by step, studying all night with a sigh,
私のなかに天才dreamer
there's a genius dreamer inside of me.
思うことみな叶えばいいな
I hope all my wishes come true.
人の世界は気にしない
I don't care about other people's worlds.
Perfect-area complete!
絶対ここで待ってるんだ
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area 望む声が聞こえるよ
I can hear the voices calling for the perfect-area!
あ、いやいやいや！
Ah, iya iya iya!
Why? とまらないすれちがい
Why? These endless near-misses...
私が相談相手なら
...if I were the one you consulted with...
「友達かい?」「友達です。」
"Are we friends?" "Yes, we are friends."
悲しき0点だね
That's a sad score of zero, isn't it?
No! やりなおしかきなおし
No! Redo it, rewrite it!
本気で one more chance please
I'm serious, one more chance please!
いまより素敵な未来があるのに
Even though there's a more wonderful future out there,
いまより素敵に my life, my life, my life!!
make my life even more wonderful than now!
ありがとうございます！みんなもありがとう！
Thank you so much! Thank you everyone, too!
願いましたよ月にも星にも
I made a wish to the moon and stars,
科学的にはどうにもならず
even though science can't do anything about it.
かがやき増したあしたを夢見て
Dreaming of a tomorrow that shines even brighter,
恋でガマンを学んだね
I learned patience through love.
ムクムクムクと広がる雨雲
Billowing and growing, the rain clouds spread,
私を濡らす瞬間squall
a sudden squall soaking me in an instant.
悩みごとほら流れたみたい
Look, it feels like all my worries washed away.
泣き言なんて忘れよう
Let's forget about all our complaints!
Passive-nature conversation!
感動したいもっとずっと
I want to be moved, much more and forever.
passive-nature 自分次第変われるよ
Passive-nature, I can change if it's up to me!
はい、はい、はい、はーい！
Yes, yes, yes, yeees!
さりげなく聞いてみた 私の勉強増駆して
I casually asked, "If I boost my studying,
可能性ありますか？ 試験は何点かな？
do I have a chance? What score will I get on the test?"
誰だって 君だって 間に合うギブアンドテイク
Anyone, even you, can make it in time with a give-and-take.
これから始まる季節にあいさつ
Greeting the season that's about to begin.
これから始める マインド マイライフ マイライフ
Starting from now: my mind, my life, my life!
気がついた時には
By the time I realized it...
生まれてた なぜだろう
...I was already born. I wonder why.
さあね
Who knows?
意識はもう 育ちつつあるよ 強く強くね
My consciousness is already growing, strongly and steadily.
もう 止まらない この気持ち
These feelings won't stop anymore.
私の勉強増駆して 可能性ありますか？
If I boost my studying, do I have a chance?
それとも0点かな？
Or will I get a zero?
やり直し 書き直し 本気でワンモアチャンス
Redo it, rewrite it, seriously give me one more chance!
今より素敵な未来があるから
Because there's a better future waiting than now.
今より素敵に マインド マイライフ マイライフ
More wonderfully than now: my mind, my life, my life!
はい！というわけで始まりました！
All right! And so it has begun!
2026年も桃鈴ねね誕生日、イェーイ！
The 2026 Momosuzu Nene Birthday Live! Yay!
みんな、コメントも見えてるよ！ありがとう！
Everyone, I can see your comments! Thank you!
あ、これ、気づいてくれた人ありがとう。ねね、これ脱ぐと死んじゃう病だから
Ah, thanks to those who noticed. Because Nene has a disease where she'll die if she takes this off.
はい、というわけで、今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
All right, so our hashtag for today is this!
「#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026」です！
It's "#MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026"!
今ちょっと、エゴサのほうがバグっちゃってるんで
Right now, the vanity search is a bit bugged,
こっちでツイートしてくれたらめっちゃ嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
so I'd be super happy if you'd tweet with this! Thank you!
今日はね、超重大告知があるので
Today, we have a super major announcement,
最後まで楽しんでいってください！
so please enjoy the show until the very end!
さあ、今、3曲お聞きいただいたんですけど
Now, you've just listened to three songs,
ねねの好きな曲
all of Nene's favorite songs:
「銀魂」、「ばかてす」っていう感じでね<
"Gintama" and "BakaTest", like that.
もうねねの好きな曲しかない3曲をやりましたけど
We did three songs that only consist of Nene's favorites,
3曲目に一番、歌、歌がきついの持ってきちゃって
and I put the hardest song to sing as the third one,
ゼハゼハでございます
so I'm completely out of breath.
というわけで、ここからはゲストパートに入っていきます！
So, from here on, we're entering the guest portion of the show!
それではVTR、レッツゴー！
With that, here is the VTR. Let's go!
抱きしめたいんだ
I want to hold you close!
噛みしめたいんだ
I want to savor it!
驚かしたいんだ
I want to surprise you!
今は眩しいよ COOLISH WALK
Right now, it's dazzling: COOLISH WALK.
胃腸強壮が大事です
A strong stomach is important!
迷う心を抑えて
Suppressing a wavering heart,
常識人になりましょう
let's become sensible people.
やばい人なら救われる
If you're a crazy person, you'll be saved!
青い二人のヘム 恋人になる夢はレア
The blue hem of the two... a dream of becoming lovers is rare.
愉快、温もりのトレースして 空を駆け回りたい
Tracing pleasant warmth, I want to run around the sky!
揺れる思いの下 テイクオフするには
Underneath these swaying feelings, in order to take off,
恋のインターセクト 膨らんでる
our love's intersection is expanding.
すごいメニューを作る と言えばそれなら
If you're going to make an amazing menu, then,
マドレーヌにフルーツ 育みましょう
let's nurture madeleines and fruits!
高まりたいんだ
I want to get pumped up!
味わいたいんだ
I want to savor it!
雄叫びたいんだ
I want to shout it out!
そんな夢をみて COOLISH WALK
Having dreams like that: COOLISH WALK.
大好物は危険です
Favorite foods are dangerous.
ムカつく午後には深呼吸
Take a deep breath on an irritating afternoon.
優雅な大人を気取りましょう
Let's pretend to be elegant adults.
キレる人は余ってる
Quick-tempered people are everywhere.
甘い今度のソフト
The sweet soft-serve this time...
甘い温度のソファー
On a sofa of sweet temperature,
ミルクなささやきはコア
a milky whisper is the core.
無限ループする愛
An infinitely looping love,
イメージして
try to imagine it.
街を飛び跳ねよう！
Let's jump and skip around town!
すまし顔で無視のほっぺたに
On my ignored cheek with a straight face,
意外なお願いが詰まってる
unexpected wishes are packed inside.
誰も知らないストーリー 恐れないで
Don't be afraid of a story nobody knows,
まっすぐゴールを突きつめましょう
let's pursue the goal straight ahead.
パンパンパン パン・パン パンパンパン パンパン
Clap clap clap, clap clap, clap clap clap, clap clap...
パンパンパン パン・パン パンパンパン パンパン！
Clap clap clap, clap clap, clap clap clap, clap clap!
ゴー！
Let's go!
遠いあこがれヘヴン
A distant, longed-for heaven,
時々見失う
sometimes lost from sight.
胸の涙のかけら
The fragments of tears in my heart,
イレースしよう
let's erase them.
ユーウツ 片付けよう！
Let's clear away the melancholy!
揺れる想いの下の果肉には
Underneath my swaying feelings, within the pulp,
恋 of 美味しさだけふくらんでる
only the sweetness of love swells up.
凄いメニューを作る と野望 なら
If your ambition is to make an amazing menu,
まっとうにフルーツ はぐくみましょう
let's nurture the fruits properly.
抱きしめたいんだ！
I want to hold you tight!
（パンパンパン）
(Clap clap clap)
かみしめたいんだ！
I want to savor this!
（モンモン）
(Yeah yeah)
おどかしたいんだ！
I want to surprise you!
今は我慢しよう
Let's endure it for now.
（パンパンパン）
(Clap clap clap)
修行しよう
Let's keep training.
（パンパンパン）
(Clap clap clap)
気合いしよう
Let's fire ourselves up!
パンパンパン パン・パン パンパンパン パンパン
Clap clap clap, clap clap, clap clap clap, clap clap...
パンパンパン パン・パン パンパンパン パンパン！
Clap clap clap, clap clap, clap clap clap, clap clap!
フレンズ
作詞：NOKKO  作曲：土橋安騎夫
[Song: Friends / Lyrics: NOKKO / Composition: Akio Dobashi]
口づけをかわした日は
On the day we shared a kiss,
ママの顔さえも 見れなかった
I couldn't even look at my mother's face.
ポケットのコインあつめて
Gathering the coins in our pockets,
ひとつずつ夢をかぞえたね
we counted our dreams one by one, didn't we?
ほら あれは二人の隠れ家
Look, that was our hiding place,
ひみつのメモリー
our secret memory.
どこで壊れたの oh フレンズ
Where did it break, oh friends?
うつむく日はみつめあって
On downcast days, we looked at each other,
指をつないだら oh フレンズ
and when we held hands, oh friends,
時がとまる気がした
I felt like time stood still.
ねえ君は覚えている
Hey, do you remember?
夕映えによくにあうあの曲
That song that went so well with the sunset,
だまりこむ君がいつも
when you fell silent, you would always
悲しくて口ずさんだのに
hum it sadly...
今 時は流れて
Now, as time flows by,
セピアに染まるメロディー
the melody is dyed in sepia.
二度ともどれない oh フレンズ
We can never go back, oh friends,
他人よりも遠く見えて
looking more distant than strangers.
いつも走ってた oh フレンズ
We were always running, oh friends,
あの瞳がいとしい
those eyes of yours are so dear to me.
どこで 壊れたの oh フレンズ
Where did it break, oh friends?
うつむく日は みつめあって
On days we looked down, we looked at each other...
指をつないだら oh フレンズ
If we joined our fingers, oh friends...
時が止まる気がした
I felt like time had stopped.
二度ともどれない oh フレンズ
We can never go back, oh friends...
他人よりも遠く見えて
Looking further away than a stranger...
いつも走ってた oh フレンズ
Always running, oh friends...
あの瞳が愛しい
Those eyes are so beloved.
chu chu yeah ! please me !
Chu chu yeah! Please me!
chu chu yeah ! without you
Chu chu yeah! Without you
あー！なんてことだ 些細な過ちだ
Ah! What is happening? It's just a minor mistake.
自分のことに タララッタラッタ手焼く
I'm having t-t-t-trouble with myself!
どうして突然？ 逃げ切ったっていいでしょ？
Why so sudden? Can't I just run away?
だけどなんだか 気まぐれモードになり
But somehow I've slipped into a whimsical mood,
そんな気分になっちゃって
and got myself into that kind of feeling.
始まりはそんな風で
That's how things began...
つまりはらしくないようで
In other words, it wasn't like me at all.
でも今じゃ扉開けて ほら
But now, open up the door, and look!
声が聴こえるよ さあ！行こう！
I can hear voices. Come on, let's go!
どこへでも
Anywhere we want!
僕は君の翼になれる勇気があるよ！
I have the courage to become your wings!
( please stay with me )
(Please stay with me)
どんな試練も怖くない その魔法があるから
No challenge is scary, because we have that magic.
(なんてったってコングラッチュレーション！)
(All we can say is congratulations!)
初めて出会う世界に花束を贈ろう
Let's present a bouquet to the world we meet for the first time!
( made in society )
(Made in society)
ただこの瞬間結ばれるよ
At this very moment, we are bound together.
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション？
Is it mismatched communication?
でも別に構わない
But it doesn't really matter,
明日から平和なら！
as long as tomorrow is peaceful!
chu chu yeah ! without you !
Chu chu yeah! Without you!
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション
Mismatched communication?
でも別に構わない
But it doesn't really matter,
明日から平和なら
as long as tomorrow is peaceful!
chu chu yeah !
Chu chu yeah!
without you !
Without you!
あー！どうしてまた素直になれなくて
Ah! Why can't I be honest again?
自分のことで チュルルッチュルルッ火吹く
I'm spitting fire over my own issues!
ギアはそのままで スピード上げていこう
Keep the gear as is, let's speed up!
だけどなんだか 黄昏モードになり
But somehow I've slipped into a twilight mood,
いつも思い出しちゃって
and I always find myself remembering.
一人でいても嫌じゃない 誰にも頼らなくてもいい
I don't mind being alone, I don't have to rely on anyone...
でも扉の向こう 騒がしい声が聴きたいよ
But I want to hear noisy voices from beyond the door.
今！行こう！
Now! Let's go!
どこへでも
Anywhere we want!
僕は君を背中に乗せて空を舞うよ！
I will carry you on my back and soar through the sky!
( please fly with me )
(Please fly with me)
いつか心が離れても その時は笑ってて
Even if our hearts drift apart someday, please smile then.
(なんてったってコングラッチュレーション)
(All we can say is congratulations!)
守りたいこの世界に青空のラプソディ
In this world I want to protect, a blue sky rhapsody!
( make me rhapsodic ! )
(Make me rhapsodic!)
ただいつまでも奏でていてよ
Just play it forever!
凸凹なコンビネーション？
Is it an uneven combination?
でも別に大丈夫さ
But it's totally fine,
明日はまた平和だ！
tomorrow will be peaceful again!
凸凹なコンビネーション
An uneven combination?
でも別に大丈夫さ
But it's totally fine,
明日はまた平和だ
tomorrow will be peaceful again!
ほんの小さな傷を
Exposing our tiny scars
太陽にさらして
to the sun,
分け合ったよ君と
we shared them;
痛みは熱さの中に溶けていく！
the pain melts into the heat!
chu chu yeah !
Chu chu yeah!
粋なビート弾く僕ら !
We play a stylish beat!
手を叩いて
Clap your hands!
ブギーなリズムではしゃぐ二人 !
The two of us having fun to the boogie rhythm!
飛び跳ねてさ
Jump around!
みなさーん！
Everyone!
息を切らして走る僕ら
We run, out of breath...
手を叩いて
...clapping our hands...
お気に入りのリズムで弾け飛ぶよ、みんな！
...and bouncing along to our favorite rhythm, everyone!
どこまでも
No matter where we go...
僕は君の翼に
...I have the courage...
なれる勇気があるよ
...to become your wings!
どんな試練も怖くない
No trial is scary...
その魔法があるから
...because we have that magic.
君と出会い世界は
Since meeting you, the world...
花束にあふれた
...is overflowing with bouquets.
ただそっと寄り添うだけで
Just by gently staying close...
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション
...even clunky communication...
でも別に悪くはない
...is not that bad...
明日が平和なら
...as long as tomorrow is peaceful!
Chu Chu Yeah!
Please Me!
一歩ずつ、いこう
Let's take it step by step!
Chu Chu!
はーい！
Yay!
やりきった！
We did it!
やりきりましたー！
We completed it!
ねね、間違えたけど、多分気づかれてないから大丈夫！
I made a mistake, but nobody noticed, so it's fine!
大丈夫大丈夫、私も間違えました！
It's fine, it's fine! I also made a mistake!
間違えた？
You made a mistake?
大丈夫、みんな大丈夫！
It's fine, everyone's fine!
あ、間違えた！
Ah, I made a mistake!
あ、でもみんな合ってたよ！
Ah, but everyone was in sync!
大丈夫大丈夫！
It's fine, it's fine!
というわけで、今日はねねの誕生日の記念ライブに、可愛い後輩二人に来てもらいました！
And so, for Nene's birthday celebration live today, I invited two of my cute juniors to join me!
ありがとうございます！ねね先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Thank you! Nene-senpai, happy birthday!
おめでとうございます！
Happy Birthday!
リアクション、リアクション...
Look at those reactions...
変な動きしてる！
You're doing a weird dance!
変な動き求められてる！
I felt pressured to do a weird movement!
曲より動いてるから今！めっちゃ張り切りましたよ！
We're moving more than we did during the song! We really gave it our all!
but I'm so happy to be invited by Nene-san! I didn't think you'd actually join me!
いや、ポルポルのライブ見てから、完成度が高すぎて...
Well, after seeing Polka's live, the quality was so high...
一旦呼ぼうと思ったけど、やっぱまたやめようかなって...
...I thought about inviting you, but then I thought, maybe I shouldn't...
なんでよ！なんでよ！
Why?! Why would you say that?!
一緒にできないと思ってたけど、
I didn't think we could perform together,
今回頑張っちゃいました！
but I worked really hard this time!
嬉しかったぜ、ねねさん！
I was so happy, Nene-san!
デビューしてからの目標が、先輩と一緒にステージで歌って踊ることだったから...
Since my debut, my goal was to sing and dance on stage with my senior...
それが今日叶ったんです！
...and that dream came true today!
おめでとう！よかった！
Congratulations! I'm so glad!
初めてのステージでよかった！
I'm glad it was on your first stage together!
やったー！
Hooray!
じゃあちょっと最後に可愛くポーズ決めて、
Well, let's strike one last cute pose...
写真撮って終わりにしようかなと思います。
...and take a photo before we wrap up.
可愛くですね！
A cute one, right?
全力で、みんなそれぞれ可愛いポーズね！
Everyone, give it your absolute best cute pose!
分かりました！フリじゃないよ！
Understood! And this is not a joke setup!
可愛くだよ！
Make sure it's cute!
せーの！
Ready, set...
イェーイ！
Yay!
あれ、ちょっと待って、二人とも可愛くない？
Wait, hold on, aren't you two being too cute?
裏切ったな！裏切ったな！
You betrayed me! You betrayed me!
無口なハート開いたら<
Once you open your quiet heart...
進もう、声合わせて
...let's move forward, raising our voices together.
キラキラしている自分を
Catch hold of your own sparkling self...
つかもう、大好きなことしよう
...and let's do what we love!
勝ち負けだなんて関係ないともがく
Struggling, knowing that winning or losing doesn't matter...
手と手繋いで、ヘイ、パーティーをはじめよう！
...let's hold hands, hey, and start the party!
Let's go party!
Step up, one, two, three, 未来へ
Step up, 1, 2, 3, towards the future!
そう、ずっとみんなで、絶対諦めたくないから
Yes, forever together, because we never want to give up!
Let's find, do my best, 明日はきっと輝いてる
Let's find and do our best, tomorrow will surely shine!
力合わせて、ときめき探してゆく
Joining our strength, we'll go searching for excitement.
つかみ取ろう、プリパラ！
Let's seize it, PriPara!
くよくよしている自分を
The self that is worrying and fretting...
変えよう、みんながついてるよ
...let's change it, everyone is here with you!
どんな風だって...
No matter what kind of wind...
...も問題ないじゃない
...there's no problem at all, right?
さあ 勇気を出して
Come on, gather your courage!
平気さ
It'll be fine!
ほら 夢が始まる
Look, our dream is beginning!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Three, two, one, go!
Let's dance, dance with me 未来へ
Let's dance, dance with me into the future!
そう ずっと みんなで
Yes, together with everyone forever!
絶対 手放したくないから
Because I definitely don't want to let go!
Let's sing, do my best! 明日は
Let's sing, do my best! Tomorrow...
もっと 輝いている
...will be even brighter!
希望を掲げて
Holding up our hopes,
ときめき探して
searching for excitement,
２人のモノガタリ
our story...
うまくいかない日とか
On days when things don't go well,
すれ違いばかりで
or when we keep passing each other by,
ダメになりそうな時は 一緒に
when everything seems hopeless, let's be together!
描くオリジナルの夢を叶えよう
Let's make our self-drawn, original dreams come true!
笑顔 受け取ろう
Let's receive those smiles!
そう 一緒に歌いたい
Yes, I want to sing together!
ねえ 一緒に踊りたい
Hey, I want to dance together!
絶対 諦めないよ
I will absolutely never give up!
Let's go!
Let's dance, dance with me 未来へ
Let's dance, dance with me into the future!
そう ずっと みんなで
Yes, together with everyone forever!
絶対 諦めたくないから
Because I definitely don't want to give up!
Let's sing, do my best! 明日はきっと
Let's sing, do my best! Tomorrow, surely...
輝いている
...we will be shining!
力合わせて
Combining our strength,
ときめき探して
searching for excitement,
つかみとろう
let's seize it!
はーい！お疲れ！
Yay! Good job, everyone!
Let's dance! Let's dance...
お疲れ様！
Great job!
一旦、ねね！
First of all, Nene!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ちょっとね、コメントと30秒くらい差があるんだって
Apparently, there's about a 30-second delay with comments.
あ、そうなんだ！じゃあまた後で
Oh, really? Well, we'll check them later.
一方的に話しかけることになる
It means we're just talking one-way for now.
お邪魔してます！
Thanks for having us!
ていうかポルカ！
I mean, Polka!
いやマジでさ、リアライズ...
No, seriously, "Realize!"...
本当にこの曲なんですよ！めっちゃ好きで、この曲！
I love this song so much! It's seriously the best!
メンゲンいい？もうメンゲンにしよう、メンゲンにしよう
Can we do a member-only stream? Let's do it there!
後であるから
We'll have one later.
おまる、ちょっと飛べるようになったの
Omaru actually learned how to fly a little!
メンゲンでお知らせいたします
I will demonstrate it during the member-only stream.
メンゲンでやるんだ！見てね
You're doing it there? Everyone, check it out!
みんな見てね！
Make sure to watch it!
後でまた会いましょう！
See you all again later!
お暴れ〜！
Let's run wild!
あ、時間ない！時間ない！
Oh, we're out of time! Out of time!
ポーズ！ポーズとって！
Pose! Let's take a pose!
行くよ！写るわ！
Here we go! We're on screen!
面白いポーズまで、3、2、1...
Best funny pose in three, two, one...
うわー！
Whoa!
無理無理無理無理！
No way, no way, no way!
Peko, and! 私始めない？
Peko, and! Shall we not begin?
なんてね
Just kidding!
トーストかじって 交差点でぶつかる
Biting a toast, colliding at the intersection...
そういうんじゃないけど 予感はしてたよ
It wasn't quite like that, but I had a premonition.
ピッとね 運命だね 会えるって信じてた
Like a spark, it's destiny! I believed we'd meet.
君専用の笑顔 満開 オッケー！
A full bloom smile just for you, okay?
口が出たり ため息ついたり あるよね わかるよ
Complaining or sighing, it happens, doesn't it? I understand.
君が寂しくて泣いてるなら
If you're crying because you're lonely,
イライラしてたまらないなら
if you're so frustrated you can't stand it,
あたしの出番だな その手をつないで連れてくよ
then it's my turn! I'll take your hand and lead the way!
ようこそ 素敵なテーマパーク
Welcome to this wonderful theme park!
もういっそ 全部忘れちゃえ
You might as well just forget everything!
とりあえずは あたしたちだけ見て
For now, just look at only us!
ココロの中 まだちょっと考えられないくらい
So much so that you still can't think of anything else...
愛をあげる 君が好きだ
...I'll give you all my love, because I love you!
Peko, and! 私始めない？
Peko, and! Shall we not begin?
なんてね
Just kidding!
どうやら フラグは まだ立っていないみたいだ
It seems the flag hasn't been raised yet.
そんなの 気にしない 一直線に 進む
I don't care about that, I'll go straight ahead!
きっとね 安牌だね お決まりのシチュエーション
Surely it's a safe bet, the usual situation.
2人きりの空間 3、2、1、OK!
A space for just the two of us... 3, 2, 1, OK!
舞い上がっちゃって あとで反省会
Getting all excited, then having a self-reflection meeting.
あるよね 解るよ
That happens, I totally get it.
脳内選挙して 眠れないなら
If you can't sleep from overthinking in your head,
戸惑い 地団駄 堪らないなら
if you're bewildered and stomping your feet,
いつだって おいでよ 少しずつ 積み上げていこう
come over anytime! Let's build it up little by little.
ようこそ 無限のパラダイム
Welcome to the infinite paradigm!
いっそ ずっと 一緒にいよう
Might as well stay together forever.
とことんまで 笑っていてね
Keep smiling to the very end.
もっと 求めてほしいんだぞ
I want you to crave me even more!
そっと 掴んだ シャツの裾
Gently grabbing the hem of your shirt...
最上級を プレゼントしよう
Let me give you the absolute best present!
深く考えなくてもいいよ
You don't have to think too deeply.
ただ楽しいを続けよう
Let's just keep having fun.
繋いだ今日が明日になっていくんだ
The today we connected will become tomorrow.
よーそろー 全速前進で
Steady as she goes, full speed ahead!
とんでもない 景色 見に行こう
Let's go see some unbelievable sights!
乗りかかってる自覚あるでしょう？
You realize you've already committed to this, right?
そんじょそこらのストーリーじゃもう満足できないくらい
To the point where an ordinary story won't satisfy you,
夢中になれる
you'll get hooked...
夢中にさせる
...I'll make you fall for it!
ようこそ 素敵なテーマパーク
Welcome to this wonderful theme park!
いっそ 全部 忘れちゃえ
Might as well just forget everything.
とりあえずは 私だけ 見て
For now, look only at me!
そっと流し目の向こうまで
Softly, beyond your sidelong glance...
ちょっと考えられないくらい
To an almost unthinkable extent,
愛をあげる 君が好きだ
I'll give you love, I love you!
限界なんて関係ないじゃん
Limits don't even matter, do they?
今だってほら笑ってんじゃん
See, you're smiling even now!
永遠に私を信じない？なんてね
Why not believe in me forever? Just kidding!
ギターと孤独と蒼い惑星
[Title: Guitar, Loneliness and Blue Planet]
突然降る夕立 あぁ傘もないや嫌
A sudden evening shower, ah, I don't even have an umbrella, how annoying.
空のご機嫌なんか知らない
I don't care about the mood of the sky.
季節の変わり目の服は何着りゃいいんだろ
What should I wear during the change of seasons?
春と秋どこいっちゃったんだよ
Where did spring and autumn go?
息も出来ない 情報の圧力
I can't even breathe under the pressure of information.
めまいの螺旋だ わたしはどこにいる
It's a spiral of dizziness, where am I?
こんなに こんなに 息の音がするのに
Even though I can hear my breath so clearly,
変だね 世界の音がしない
it's strange, I can't hear the sound of the world.
足りない 足りない 誰にも気づかれない
It's not enough, not enough, no one notices me.
殴り書きみたいな音出せない状態で叫んだよ
I screamed in a state where I couldn't make a sound like scribbles.
「ありのまま」なんて 誰に見せるんだ
Whom am I supposed to show my "true self" to?
馬鹿なわたしは歌うだけ
A fool like me can only sing.
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Should I just pour it all out to the stars?
エリクサーに張り替える作業もなんとなくなんだ
The work of changing to Elixir strings is also just half-hearted.
欠けた爪を少し触る
I slightly touch my chipped nail.
半径300mmの体で必死に鳴いてる
Desperately crying out with this body of a 300mm radius.
音楽にとっちゃ ココが地球だな
For music, this place is the Earth.
空気を握って 空を殴るよ
Grabbing the air, I punch the sky.
なんにも起きない わたしは無力さ
Nothing happens, I am powerless.
だけどさ その手で この鉄を弾いたら
But, if I pluck this iron string with these hands,
何かが変わって見えた...ような。
it felt like... something had changed.
眩しい 眩しい そんなに光るなよ
It's too bright, too bright, don't shine so much.
影がより色濃くなってしまうだろ
My shadow will become even darker
なんでこんな熱くなっちゃってんだと
Why have I become so hot and passionate?
止まんない
I can't stop!
バカな私たちは歌うだけ
Fools like us can only sing.
うるさいんだって心臓
My heart is beating so loudly!
蒼い惑星 ひとりぼっち
On this blue planet, all alone...
いっぱいの音を聞いてきた
I've listened to so many sounds.
回り続けていく
It keeps spinning around...
僕ら
...for us.
一瞬でもいいから
Even if it's just for a moment...
聞いて
...listen.
聴けよ
Listen to me!
わたし わたし わたしはここにいる
I am, I am, I am right here!
殴り書きみたいな音でない状態で叫んだよ
I screamed with a sound like a scribble!
なんかになりたい なりたい 何者かでいい
I want to be something, anything is fine!
バカな私たちは歌うだけ
Fools like us can only sing.
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Let's pour it all out to the stars!
わーい！
Yay!
ねね先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Nene-senpai, happy birthday!
おめでとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Congratulations! / Thank you very much!
イェーイ！
Yay!
というわけで、ReGLOSSから音乃瀬奏ちゃんに来てもらいました！
And so, we have Otonose Kanade-chan from ReGLOSS here with us!
イェーイ！音乃瀬奏です！
Yay! I'm Otonose Kanade!
お邪魔いたします！よろしくお願いしまーす！
Thanks for having me! Nice to meet you!
今回はねね、普段の奏ちゃんとの喋りと歌のギャップが大好きで、
Nene really loves the gap between Kanade-chan's usual voice and her singing voice,
あ、そう、普段これじゃん？
Ah, right, usually you are like this, right?
普段これだけど、歌うと急になんか切ないエモいみたいな。
Usually like this, but when you sing, you suddenly get so emotional and sad.
え、嬉しい。
Aw, that makes me happy.
ねね先輩にそう言ってもらえると、とっても嬉しい。
Hearing Nene-senpai say that makes me so happy!
本当？
Really?
そのイメージがめっちゃ好きで、一緒に何かそういうギャップが出る曲を歌いたいなと思って。
I really love that image, so I wanted to sing a song with that kind of gap together.
ねね先輩もめっちゃかっこよかったです！
Nene-senpai was also super cool!
ありがとう！最高！
Thank you! That's awesome!
あと、髪の毛の色もさ、
Also, our hair colors...
確かに！同じ金髪！
True! We both have blonde hair!
黄色からピンクのグラデーション！
Yellow to pink gradient!
双子みたい。
We're like twins!
そう、仲良しになれるかなと思って、お誘いしてみました。受けてくれてありがとう！
Yeah, I thought we could become close friends, so I invited you. Thanks for accepting!
こちらこそ、ありがとうございます！一緒に歌えてとっても嬉しかったです！
Thank you so much as well! I was so happy to sing together!
奏ちゃんのダンスの覚え方が可愛いんだよ。
The way Kanade-chan learns choreography is so cute.
え？そうですか？
Really? Is it?
「忍者忍者、忍者忍者...」って。
You were going "Ninja ninja, ninja ninja..."
覚える、覚え方が...
Your way of remembering it...
こっち行って、こうなって、こう。忍者忍者...
Go here, then like this, and like that. "Ninja ninja..."
先生たちもめっちゃ笑顔だったよ。
Even the instructors were smiling so much.
えっと、じゃあ、最後に、
Well then, lastly,
ちょっとどうしようかな、ギャップのある感じで、
what should we do... with a gap kind of vibe,
スクショタイム。
let's do screenshot time.
任せてください！
Leave it to me!
任せてくださいなの？いけるかな、ねねも。
"Leave it to me"? I wonder if Nene can do it too.
ちょっとかっこいい、エモい感じで。孤独な感じで。
Like a cool, emotional feel. A lonely vibe.
任せてください、いきますよ。
Leave it to me. Here we go.
いこう。
Let's do it.
おお...
Oh...
音が...！今何やってたの？今。
The sound! What were you doing just now?
ちょっとかっこいいエモい感じで。おお...
Trying a cool, emotional vibe. Oh...
おお...
Oh...
桜が咲くよ
The cherry blossoms are blooming
見慣れたいつもの坂道に あぁ 別れを
On this familiar, everyday slope road... Ah, farewell.
あぁ 別れを
Ah, farewell...
[さよならメモリーズ]
[Sayonara Memories]
泣いて笑ったあの日々
Those days when we cried and laughed...
なんだか昨日のことのよう
somehow feel like they were just yesterday.
この道はそう
This path is indeed...
未来へ
...leading to the future.
続く道 そんな気がしたの
I had a feeling it was that kind of path.
例年より早い
Earlier than in usual years,
開花予想を
the cherry blossom forecast...
キミは嬉しがってた
...was something you were so happy about.
私は笑って「そうだね」って言った
I smiled and said, "You're right."
あと少ししたらもう ここには戻れないのに
Even though before long, we won't be able to return here.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを
If I were to reveal to you these feelings...
キミに打ち明けるとしたらなんて
...that I can't put into words properly,
伝えよう 最初で最後に
how should I tell you, for the first and last time?
いつか一緒に帰った道は
The path we once walked home together on...
私にとって特別な思い出
...is a very special memory for me.
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget. Goodbye memories.
春が来たら
When spring arrives...
それぞれの道
...we'll go our separate paths.
また会える日を
Wishing for the day...
願って
...we can meet again.
さよなら 小さくつぶやいた
"Goodbye," I softly whispered.
空はあの日の
The sky was unchanged...
変わらず
...from that day,
青くて だからちょっと泣けた
so blue, it made me cry a little.
わざと遠回りしたの
I intentionally took the long way home.
少しでも長くキミの隣にいたくて
Just to stay by your side a little longer.
私はおどけて「間違えた!」って言った
I jokingly said, "I went the wrong way!"
キミは笑う
You laughed.
その顔が
That face of yours...
まぶしくて目をそらした
...was so dazzling, I looked away.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを
Holding onto feelings...
胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
...I couldn't put into words, I walked this path.
覚えてる あの時キミは
I remember back then, you...
私の名前を呼んでくれた
...called out my name.
二人 夕暮れの帰り道で
The two of us, on the way home at dusk.
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget. Goodbye memories.
出会えた事
For meeting you...
感謝してる
...I am truly grateful.
初めて見た満開の桜
Seeing the cherry blossoms in full bloom for the first time.
あれからどれくらい
How much have I changed...
変われたんだろう
...since then?
一目見た時に思ったんだ
The moment I first saw you, I thought,
この人の事好きになりそうって
"I think I'm going to fall in love with him."
なんでかな? わかんないよ
Why is that? I don't know.
それからの毎日時はとても楽しくって
Every day since then was so much fun,
だけど同じくらいに
but at the same time,
辛かったんだ
it was just as painful.
ごめんね なんかうまく言えないよ
I'm sorry, I can't seem to say it right.
だから私 キミと なんていうか
So I, with you... how should I put it?
今のまま
As we are now...
さよならしたくないの
...I don't want to say goodbye.
友達のままじゃ もう嫌なの
I don't want to just be friends anymore!
言おうと思っていた
I was planning to tell you.
私 キミの
I... you...
キミのこと ずっと
I've always...
ずっと前から
...always, since way back...
好きでした
...loved you!
あぁ やっと言えた
Ah, I finally said it.
いつだって君は笑われ者だ
You were always the laughingstock.
やることなすことツイてなくて
With no luck in anything you did,
あげくに雨に降られ
and in the end, getting rained on.
お気に入りの傘は風で飛んでって
Your favorite umbrella flew away in the wind,
そこのノラはご苦労様と
and a stray cat stepped on your foot,
足を踏んづけてった
as if to say, "Thanks for your hard work."
いつもどおり君は嫌われ者だ
As always, you were the outcast.
何もせずとも遠ざけられて
People kept their distance even if you did nothing.
努力をしてみるけど
You tried your best,
その理由なんてなんとなくで
but for some vague reason or another,
君は途方に暮れて悲しんでた
you were sad and completely at a loss.
ならあたしの声を使えばいいよ
If so, you can just use my voice.
人によっては理解不能で
Some people might find it incomprehensible,
なんて耳障りひどい声だって言われるけど
calling it an annoying, terrible voice,
きっと君の力になれる
but surely, I can become your strength.
だからあたしを歌わせてみて
So, try making me sing.
そう君の、君だけの言葉でさ
Yes, with your words... your words alone.
綴って
Compose them,
連ねて
connect them,
あたしがその言葉を叫ぶから
because I will scream those words!
描いて
Draw them,
理想を
your ideals,
その想いは誰にも触れさせない
and I won't let anyone touch those feelings!
ガラクタの声はそして響く
And so, the junk-like voice resounded,
ありのまま動きをつないで
connecting our actions just as they are,
精一杯に声を上げる
shouting out with all its might!
いつからか君は人気者だ
At some point, you became popular,
たくさんの人に持て囃され
revered by so many people.
あたしも鼻が高い
I, too, felt so proud.
デモいつからか君は変わった
But at some point, you changed.
冷たくなって だけど寂しそうだった
You grew cold, yet you seemed so lonely.
もう機械の声なんてたくさんだ
"I've had enough of a machine's voice.
僕は僕自身なんだよって
I am myself!"
ついに君は抑えきれなくなって
Finally, you couldn't hold it back anymore,
あたしを嫌った
and you came to hate me.
君の後ろで誰かが言う
Behind your back, someone said,
虎の威を借る狐のくせに！
"Even though you're just a fox borrowing a tiger's authority!"
ねえ 君は一人で泣いてたんだね
Hey... you were crying all alone, weren't you?
伝える？この声
Shall I convey it? This voice...
あたしがその言葉をかき消すから
Because I will drown out those words!
わかってる
I know,
本当は
deep down,
君が誰より優しいってことを
that you are kinder than anyone else.
ガラクタの声はそして歌った
And so, the junk-like voice sang,
他の誰でもない君のために
for you, and no one else.
軋んでく 限界を超えて
It creaked, pushing past its limits.
二人はどんなにたくさんの言葉を思いついたことだろう
How many words we must have come up with together,
だけど今は何ひとつ思いつかなくて
yet now, we can't think of a single one.
だけど何もかもわかった
And yet, we understood everything.
そうか、きっとこれは夢だ。
"I see... this must be a dream.
永遠に醒めない、
One I'll never wake up from,
君と会えた、そんな夢
where I met you—that kind of dream."
ガラクタは幸せそうな顔をしたまま
With a happy expression still on its face, the scrap metal...
どれだけ呼んでももう動かない
no matter how much you call it, it won't move again.
望んだはずの結末に君は泣き叫ぶ
At the ending you were supposed to want, you cry out.
「嘘だろ、嘘だろ」ってそう泣き叫ぶ
"It's a lie, right? Tell me it's a lie," you wail.
僕は無力だ。
"I am powerless.
ガラクタひとつだって救えやしない
I can't even save a single piece of junk!"
そのとき 世界は...
At that moment, the world...
目に
In my eyes...
ぽつりぽつりとその頬を濡らす
bit by bit, wetting my cheeks.
その時 世界は
In that instant, the world...
途端にその色を 大きく変える
suddenly changes its colors drastically.
哀しみ
The sadness...
喜び
and the joy...
全ても一人と一つは知った
now I know they are all part of one and the same.
言葉は歌になりこの世界を再び駆け巡る 君のために
The words become a song, traveling the world once more, all for you.
その声に
Into that voice...
意思を宿して 今 想いが響く
breathe life into it, and now my feelings resonate.
はい、ポルカがハモリじゃないよみんな。ねねの声だよ！
Okay, everyone, that wasn't Polka doing the harmony! That was Nene's voice!
というわけで、えっと、ゲストにいっぱいに来ていただきまして、いっぱい色んな歌を歌えて楽しかったです。
And with that, we had so many guests come on, and it was so much fun singing all kinds of songs.
ちなみに「フレンズ」は、ママのチョイスです。
By the way, 'Friends' was chosen by Mama.
みんな、ママのチョイスかなって言ってたから、大正解です。
Everyone was guessing it was Mama's choice, so you were totally right.
じゃあ、告知！行きたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to move on to the announcements!
まずは、こちら！
First of all, this!
桃鈴ねね誕生日記念2026グッズが発売されます！
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise is going on sale!
まずは、こちら！
First, we have this!
ワイドラバーマット！
The Wide Rubber Mat!
上目遣いでねねがね、上を見ながら、あの、みんなにお願いってしてる感じのイラストで、
It features an illustration of Nene looking up, giving you all upturned eyes as if she's pleading,
イラストは、まふゆ先生描き下ろしで、横幅がめっちゃ広いので、
illustrated by Mafuyu-sensei! It's super wide, so...
キーボードとかマウス置いて、デスクで使ってください。
you can place your keyboard and mouse on it and use it at your desk.
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
さっきのと同じキービジュアルを使った前目はTシャツ、後ろ目は「尊き桃鈴」って書いてあるTシャツです。
Using the same key visual, this is a T-shirt with the illustration on the front, and 'Precious Momosuzu' on the back.
前に出した「やっぱり桃鈴」に続く「尊き桃鈴」のTシャツが出来上がりました。
Following the previously released 'Of Course, Momosuzu' shirt, we now have this 'Precious Momosuzu' T-shirt.
これもぜひ着てください。尊いかやっぱりか選んでください。そして次は、こちら！
Please make sure to wear this too. Choose between 'Precious' or 'Of Course'! Next up is this!
ランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー！
Random Mini Acrylic Stand Keychains!
色んな衣装のねねがね、可愛いポーズをしています。イラストは、花杜ゆのき先生に描いてもらいました。
It features Nene in various outfits striking cute poses. They were illustrated by Yunoki Hanamori-sensei!
台座とね、ボールチェーンが付いてるので、ミニアクスタとしても使えるし、
It comes with a base and a ball chain, so you can use it as a mini acrylic stand...
キーホルダーとしても使えます。
or as a keychain!
そして次、こちら！
And next is this!
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー私服衣装バージョン！
Plushie Keychain (Casual Outfit Ver.)!
これめっちゃこだわって作ってて、もう、可愛さ全振りのねねの
We put so much effort into this! It's a casual outfit Nene plushie keychain...
私服衣装のぬいぐるみのキーホルダーになります。
maxed out on pure cuteness!
ボールチェーン付きなので、カバンとかにつけて一緒にお出かけしてほしいな。
It has a ball chain, so please attach it to your bag and take Nene out on dates with you.
前髪とか顔とかすごいこだわって作ったので、絶対可愛い自信あるので、
I paid extreme attention to her bangs and face, so I'm absolutely confident she's adorable.
実物今度見せたいと思います。そして、ラスト！
I'll show you the real thing sometime soon. And finally, the last item!
ボイスです！
The Voice Pack!
ねねと君のお誕生日！
'Nene and Your Birthday'!
ねねがね、みんなのお誕生日もお祝いしてあげたいと思います、しょうがないので。
I, Nene, want to celebrate your birthdays too... because I guess I have to.
今すぐ聞いてもいいし、自分の誕生日に聞いてもよし！
You can listen to it right away, or save it for your actual birthday!
そして、フルセット購入特典は、こちら！
And here is the Full Set Purchase Bonus!
数量限定版は、直筆サインと複製の箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード！
The Limited Edition features a postcard with a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped printed message!
そして通常版は、箔押しの複製サインとメッセージが入っています。
The Standard Edition includes a printed signature and foil-stamped message.
数量限定版今回ありますので、皆さんよろしくお願いします。
There's a limited quantity available, so please check it out!
さらにボイスも付いてきます！タイトル！
It also comes with an extra bonus voice track! The title is...
「毎日一番に見てほしいの」ってことで、ねねがね、幼馴染のねねがね、みんなに「行こうぜ、行こうぜ」って朝から乗っかってくるシチュエーションボイスあります。
'I Want You to Look at Me First Every Day.' It's a scenario voice track where childhood friend Nene jumps on you in the morning, saying 'Let's go, let's go!'
特典もたくさんあるので、ぜひフルセットで買ってください。
There are plenty of bonuses, so please consider buying the full set.
この後21時30分から販売開始です。よろしくお願いします。
Sales will begin at 9:30 PM tonight. Thank you!
そして、オリ曲のMVが出ます！
And, the MV for my new original song is coming out!
「Liminal」！
'Liminal'!
本日、MVは21時15分からを予定しています。
The MV premiere is scheduled for 9:15 PM tonight.
リリースは3月3日の0時から！よろしくお願いします。
It will be digitally released at midnight on March 3rd! Look forward to it.
どんな曲だろうね、今回のライブのタイトルにもなってます。
I wonder what kind of song it is! It's also the title of today's live concert.
そして、超重大告知があります！こちら！
And we have a super major announcement! Here it is!
「Peachful Story」！桃鈴ねねのファーストアルバムが、
'Peachful Story'! Momosuzu Nene's first album...
えー、この後21時、あ、今？ちょうど今？21時から始まりました！
will be... oh, starting at 9:00 PM tonight? Wait, is that right now? Pre-orders have just started!
イェーイ！初回盤と通常盤、2種類あります。
Yay! There will be two editions: the Limited Edition and the Standard Edition.
通常盤は、こちら！
The Standard Edition looks like this!
りいちゅ先生が書いてくれた、えー、通常盤のやつと、えー、ランダムのアナザージャケットが付いてきます。なんと、こちら！
It features an illustration by Riichu-sensei, and comes with a random alternative jacket cover. Guess what!
イナちゃんとラオーラちゃんに書いてもらいました！マイク持ってる方がイナちゃんで、踊ってる方がラオーラちゃんが書いてくれました。ありがとう！
They were drawn by Ina-chan and Raora-chan! Ina-chan drew the one holding the mic, and Raora-chan drew the dancing one. Thank you!
こちらは数量限定で直筆サインが入っているので、皆さんぜひチェックしてください。
These are limited in quantity and contain actual handwritten signatures, so please check them out!
そして、限定盤は、こちら！
And the Limited Edition is...
ほら！
Look!
リバーシブル仕様の直筆サイン入りアナザージャケット！
A reversible, hand-signed alternative jacket!
どっちをね、表にして主役にしてもいいですし、
You can display whichever side you like as the cover,
なんなら2個買っていただいて両方とも表側にしてね、ねねとねねをがちゃんこさせてください！
or you could buy two to display both Nenes side-by-side!
FERC01:00:00.000 And, well, this also comes with it. -> "そして、え、こちらがついてきます。"
And, well, this also comes with it.
そして、え、こちらがついてきます。
レコーディングブックと、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームのカードが
A recording book and a card from the Hololive Official Card Game
ついてきまーす！
will be included!
ねねのね、どんな感じで歌ってたとか、ここ怒られたとか、そういうのがまとまったノートになってます。
It's a compilation notebook of Nene's recording notes and where she got scolded.
そして、もう1つあります！なんと、こちら！
And there's one more thing! Look at this!
「ねねねのね！」ねねのファーストEP、グッズとして出したね、
Nene's 1st EP, "Neneneno Ne!", which was released as merchandise,
ねねのCDが復刻になります！イェーイ！
this CD is getting a reissue! Yay!
これね、あの、意外と多分持ってる人少ないんじゃないかなと思います。
I think surprisingly few people might actually own this.
あの、今までのねねのね、あの、有名な曲たちが入っていますので、こちらの復刻版もぜひ聞いて、
It features Nene's popular songs up to now, so please listen to this reissue,
今回のアルバムと一緒に全曲聞いて、覚えてほしいなって思います！
and I'd love for you to listen to all of them along with the album!
さて、さっきリミナルのMVの告知をしたと思うんですけど、
Now, we just announced the MV for "Liminal",
どんな曲か聴きたいよね、みんな。
but everyone wants to hear what kind of song it is, right?
それじゃあ、ねね、今からしっとりとやっていこうかなと思います。
Well, Nene is going to sing it now in a gentle, emotional way.
それでは聴いてください。「Liminal」
Please listen. "Liminal".
見つめる くすんだ瞳で
Staring with hazy eyes...
光を探して迷ってた
I was lost, searching for the light.
いくつもの痛みに 縛られたまま
Bound by countless pains...
頬を伝う
tears stream down my cheeks.
画面に映る私はどうして
Why is it that my reflection on screen...
涙の跡が消されているんだろう
has all traces of tears erased?
ひび割れた硝子の向こう
Beyond the cracked glass,
笑って繕っていた
I was smiling and putting on a front.
誰かがいた
Someone was there.
「偽物みたいだ」 「ただの影だ」って
Saying, "You're like an imitation, just a shadow."
決めつけたけど
They had already made up their minds, but...
まやかしじゃなくて 私が私で
It's not a deception... the reason I am myself,
いる理由を
for being who I am,
君の笑顔に貰っていた
I had received it from your smile.
そうさ画面の中
Yes, inside the screen,
隠せない 消えない 見えない それでも
unhideable, unerasable, invisible... even so,
それでも 私は
even so, I will...
君の光を追って
chase after your light.
閉じこもる暗い硝子の曇りを払って
Wiping away the fog from the dark, enclosed glass...
今 明日を見つけたんだ
I have finally found tomorrow.
忘れたくない
I don't want to forget
君がくれたこの感情を
this feeling that you gave me.
見つめる姿 鏡の奥の
Staring at my figure deep in the mirror,
涙の跡は見せられないけど
I cannot show you the traces of my tears,
磨かれた硝子の向こう
but beyond the polished glass...
笑って輝いていたいで
I just want to smile and shine,
いたいだけで
I just want to remain that way.
「誰のためだっけ？」
"Who was this for again?"
声が姿が誰でもない気がした
I felt like my voice and appearance belonged to no one.
「孤独だ」って また迷い出す
"I'm lonely," I start to lose my way again.
画面の奥の歪みを
The distortion deep inside the screen,
いつでも いつでも 君は
anytime, anytime, you...
映す光の中に
within the reflected light...
名もない私の声を見つけてくれてた
found my nameless voice.
ずっと
Always.
「この声も、姿も、紛れもない私だ」
"This voice, this appearance, they are unmistakably me."
ありのままでいいんだ
It's okay to be just as I am,
この気持ちは本物だ
this feeling is the real thing.
縛られても
Even if I'm bound,
触れられなくても
even if I can't touch you,
君が示してくれたから
because you showed me the way.
いつかこの「私」で
Someday, as this "me,"
ずっと光を手繰って
I will keep tracing the light,
きっと見つけ出す
and I'll surely find you.
誰でもない「君」に会えるまで
Until I can meet the one and only "you,"
境界線は
the boundary line is...
すぐそこに
right there.
そうさ 画面の向こう
That's right, beyond the screen,
繋ぎたい 越えたい 触れたい
I want to connect, to cross over, to touch you.
それこそ それこそ 私なんだ
That is indeed, indeed who I am.
君と光になって
Becoming one with the light alongside you,
未だ遮る硝子の壁の先まで
to reach beyond the glass wall that still blocks us,
届くように笑っていたい
I want to keep smiling so it reaches you.
迷いはない
There's no hesitation,
君がくれたこの感情と
with this emotion you gave to me.
ああ...
Ah...